Catholic Charities USA
The American Catholic Research Center and University Archives
- Series 3: General Administration Files, 1920-2008; (101 Boxes)
  - Subseries 3.2: Subject (A-Z), 1961-2008; (19 Boxes)
    - Child Welfare League of America: Adoption Standards, 1967-1968 (Box 61, Folder 32)
    - Child Welfare League of America: Adoption Standards, 1969 (Box 61, Folder 33)
    - Child Welfare League of America: Advisory Committee to Foster Care Conference, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 34)
    - Child Welfare League of America: Committee on Revision of Standards for Adoption Service, 1963-1966 (Box 61, Folder 35)
    - Child Welfare League of America: Committee on Standards and Services, 1961-1963 (Box 61, Folder 36)
    - Child Welfare League of America: Committee on Standards for Services for Children in their own Homes, 1961-1963 (Box 61, Folder 37)
    - Child Welfare League of America: Day Care Project, 1961 (Box 61, Folder 38)
    - Child Welfare League of America: Practice Commission on Foster Care, 1966 (Box 61, Folder 39)
    - Child Welfare League of America: Training Courses for House Parents, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 40)
    - Child Welfare League of America: Working Committee to Formulate Standards for Group Care of Children, 1962 (Box 61, Folder 41)
    - Christ Child Society, 1963-1964 (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - Church and the Elderly, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - Citizens' Committee for Children-Children's Allowances, 1969-1970 (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Coady, Msgr. Leo J.-President of NCCC, 1961-1964 (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Coady, Msgr. Leo J.-President of NCCC, 1968-1969 (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Coalition on Human Needs and Budget Priorities, 1973 (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Coalition for Human Needs and Budget Priorities, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - Coalition for the Public Good, 1972-1973 (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Coalition for the Public Good (1), 1972-1976 (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Coalition for the Public Good (2), 1972-1976 (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - Columbus Area Council on Alcoholism, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 11)
    - Committee for National Health Insurance, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 12)
    - Committee for Population and Pro-Life Activities, 1975 (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Committee: Pro-Life (1), 1977 (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Committee: Pro-Life (2), 1977 (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Community Welfare Council, 1970 (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Comprehensive Social Service System, 1976-1977 (Box 62, Folder 17)
    - Conference of Major Superiors of Women, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 18)
    - Conference of Ministries Responsible for Social Welfare, 1968 (Box 62, Folder 19)
    - Conference of Religious, 1963 (Box 62, Folder 20)
    - Conference of Religious, 1964 (Box 62, Folder 21)
    - Conference of Religious, 1965 (Box 62, Folder 22)
    - Conference of Religious, 1966 (Box 62, Folder 23)
    - Conference of Religious, 1967 (Box 62, Folder 24)
    - Conference of Religious (1), 1968 (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Conference of Religious (2), 1968 (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Conference of Religious, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Conference of Religious, 1970 (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Congressional Comment, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Cook-in Special Event, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - Cook-in Special Event, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Cooperative League of the USA, 1969-1970 (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Coordinated Catholic Charities Appeals, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Addresses and Articles, 1965 (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Addresses, Speeches (1), 1966 (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Addresses, Speeches (2), 1966 (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Addresses and Invocations, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Addresses and Invocations, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Addresses and Invocations, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Articles and Addresses (1), 1970 (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Articles and Addresses (2), 1970 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Addresses (1), 1971 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Addresses (2), 1971 (Box 63, Folder 19)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Addresses, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 20)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Addresses and Testimony, 1974 (Box 63, Folder 21)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Addresses and Publicity, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 22)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Addresses, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 23)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Appointment to Boards, 1968-1975 (Box 63, Folder 24)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Congressional Testimony, 1966 (Box 63, Folder 25)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Congressional Testimony, 1967 (Box 63, Folder 26)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Congressional Testimony, 1968 (Box 63, Folder 27)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Congressional Testimony, 1969 (Box 63, Folder 28)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Congressional Testimony, 1972 (Box 63, Folder 29)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Congressional Testimony, 1975 (Box 63, Folder 30)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Editorials, 1976-1977 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Editorials, 1978-1980 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Invitations, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Invitations, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Invitations to Speak and Speeches (1), 1972 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Invitations to Speak and Speeches (2), 1972 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Invitations to Speak and Speeches, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Invitations to Speak and Speeches, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Invitations to Speak and Speeches, 1978 (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Messages of Congratulation, Sympathy, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 10)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Messages of Congratulations, Sympathy, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 11)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Messages of Congratulations, Sympathy, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 12)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Messages of Congratulations, Sympathy, 1977 (Box 64, Folder 13)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Messages of Congratulations, Sympathy, 1978-1979 (Box 64, Folder 14)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Memberships, 1967-1968 (Box 64, Folder 15)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Memberships, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 16)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Miscellaneous, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 17)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Notes, 1970, 1976 (Box 64, Folder 18)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Personal, 1966-1967 (Box 64, Folder 19)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Personal, 1968-1969 (Box 64, Folder 20)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Publicity, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 21)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Secretary's Report, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 22)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Secretary's Report, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 23)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Secretary's Report, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 24)
    - Corocran, Lawrence: Secretary's Report, 1970 (Box 64, Folder 25)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Secretary's Report, 1972 (Box 64, Folder 26)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Speeches, 1975-1978 (Box 64, Folder 27)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Talks, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 28)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Talks, 1966-1969 (Box 64, Folder 29)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Talks, 1970-1973 (Box 64, Folder 30)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Travel, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 31)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Travel, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 32)
    - Corcoran, Lawrence: Travel, 1968 (Box 64, Folder 33)
    - Council of Catholic Charities of Toronto, 1975-1976 (Box 64, Folder 34)
    - Council of Jewish Federations and Welfare Funds, 1972-1973 (Box 64, Folder 35)
    - Council of National Organizations for Children and Youth, 1961 (Box 64, Folder 36)
    - Council of National Organizations for Children and Youth, 1965-1966 (Box 64, Folder 37)
    - Council of National Organizations for Children and Youth, 1968-1971 (Box 64, Folder 38)
    - Council of National Priorities and Resources, 1975 (Box 64, Folder 39)
    - Council on Social Work Education, 1962-1964 (Box 64, Folder 40)
    - Council on Social Work Education, 1964 (Box 64, Folder 41)
    - Council on Social Work Education, 1965 (Box 64, Folder 42)
    - Council on Social Work Education, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 43)
    - Council on Social Work Education, 1967 (Box 64, Folder 44)
    - Council on Social Work Education, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Council on Social Work Education, 1969-1971 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Council on Social Work Education, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Council on Social Work Education, 1976 (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Cuban Refugees, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - General Correspondence D, 1961-1964 (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - General Correspondence D, 1965 (Box 65, Folder 7)
    - General Correspondence D, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - General Correspondence D, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - General Correspondence D, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - General Correspondence D, 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - General Correspondence D, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - Dall, Msgr. Norbert P., 1962-1964 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Daly, Dorothy Bird-NCCC President, 1972-1973 (Box 65, Folder 14)
    - Daly, Leo-Company, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 15)
      Architects
    - Daughters of Charity, 1970-1971 (Box 65, Folder 16)
    - Day Care Bulletin, 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 17)
    - Dean's Dinner-Phoenix, Arizona, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 18)
    - Dean's Dinner-New Orleans, Lousiana, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 19)
    - Dean's Meeting-Council on Social Education-Atlanta, Georgia, 1974 (Box 65, Folder 20)
    - Deans of Catholic Schools of Social Work and Directors of Catholic Charities-Meeting, 1968-1969 (Box 65, Folder 21)
    - Deans of Catholic Schools of Social Work and Directors of Catholic Charities-Meeting, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 22)
    - Deans of Schools of Social Work and Representatives of Catholic Charities, 1972 (Box 65, Folder 23)
    - Defense Department-U.S., 1964-1966 (Box 65, Folder 24)
    - Diocesan Bureau of Human Relations-Portland, Maine, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 25)
    - Donihi, Robert and Rosemary, 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 26)
      Public Relations
    - Donihi, Robert and Rosemary, 1966-1967 (Box 65, Folder 27)
    - Donihi, Robert and Rosemary, 1970 (Box 65, Folder 28)
    - Donihi, Robert, 1971-1972 (Box 65, Folder 29)
    - Downs, Rev. Richard J., 1961 (Box 65, Folder 30)
    - Doyle, Msgr. Michael-President, 1961-1962 (Box 65, Folder 31)
    - Dunn, Rev. Donald, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 32)
    - Dunn, Rev. Donald, 1979-1980 (Box 65, Folder 33)
    - General Correspondence E, 1961-1963 (Box 65, Folder 34)
    - General Correspondence E, 1964 (Box 65, Folder 35)
    - General Correspondence E, 1965-1966 (Box 65, Folder 36)
    - General Correspondence E, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 37)
    - General Correspondence E, 1968-1970 (Box 65, Folder 38)
    - Economic Stimulus, 1977 (Box 65, Folder 39)
    - Elwell, Rev. Clarence, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 40)
    - Equal Rights Amendment (ERA), 1978-1979 (Box 65, Folder 41)
    - Essays Submitted-Msgr. O'Grady Award, 1963 (Box 65, Folder 42)
    - Ethnic and Neighborhood Affairs-Catholic Conference, 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 43)
    - Evangelism in the American Context, 1975-1976 (Box 65, Folder 44)
      at Notre Dame University
    - F-General Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 65, Folder 45)
    - F-General Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 65, Folder 46)
    - F-General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 65, Folder 47)
    - F-General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 65, Folder 48)
    - F-General Correspondence, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 49)
    - F-General Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 65, Folder 50)
    - F-General Correspondence, 1973-1975 (Box 65, Folder 51)
    - Family Service Association of America, 1962-1964 (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Family Service Association of America, 1970-1973 (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Federal Tax Sharing, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Fees for Casework Services Workshop, 1962-1963 (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - Filer Commission (1), 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Filer Commission (2), 1973-1974 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - Filer Commission (1), 1975 (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Filer Commission (2), 1975 (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Filer Commission (1), 1976 (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Filer Commission (2), 1976 (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Ford Foundation, 1963-1966 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Foreign Files, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Foreign Files, 1967-1968 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Foreign Files, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Foreign Files, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Foster Parents Liability Insurance, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Foundation for Cooperative Housing, 1968-1969 (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Foundation for Cooperative Housing, 1969 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Foundation for Cooperative Housing, 1969-1970 (Box 66, Folder 19)
    - Foundation for Cooperative Housing, 1974-1975 (Box 66, Folder 20)
    - Foundations, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 21)
    - Freedom and Rights in Social Services, 1968-1969 (Box 66, Folder 22)
    - Fund Raising, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 23)
    - Fund Raising Institute-Chicago, Illinois, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 24)
    - G-General Correspondence, 1961-1963 (Box 66, Folder 25)
    - G-General Correspondence, 1964-1965 (Box 66, Folder 26)
    - G-General Correspondence, 1966 (Box 66, Folder 27)
    - G-General Correspondence, 1967 (Box 66, Folder 28)
    - G-General Correspondence, 1968 (Box 66, Folder 29)
    - G-General Correspondence, 1969-1970 (Box 66, Folder 30)
    - G-General Correspondence, 1975 (Box 66, Folder 31)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Addresses and Statements, 1961 (Box 66, Folder 32)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Addresses and Statements, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 33)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Addresses (1), 1963 (Box 66, Folder 34)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Addresses (2), 1963 (Box 66, Folder 35)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Addresses and Articles (1), 1964 (Box 66, Folder 36)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Addresses and Articles (2), 1964 (Box 66, Folder 37)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Addresses and Statements, 1965 (Box 66, Folder 38)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Articles, 1962 (Box 66, Folder 39)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Charity Newspaper, 1961-1965 (Box 66, Folder 40)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Material for Speaking Engagements, 1961-1962 (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Correspondence for Speaking Arrangements (1), 1962 (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Correspondence for Speaking Arrangements (2), 1962 (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Correspondence for Speaking Arrangements (3), 1962 (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Correspondence for Speaking Arrangements (1), 1963 (Box 67, Folder 5)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Correspondence for Speaking Arrangements (2), 1963 (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Correspondence-Speaking Engagements, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Correspondence, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Correspondence, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Correspondence, 1969 (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Correspondence, 1970 (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Correspondence, 1972-1973 (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Inter-Office Memos, 1961-1962 (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Invitations, 1961-1962 (Box 67, Folder 15)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Letters of Congratulations and Sympathy, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 16)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Memos and Handwritten Notes, 1961-1965 (Box 67, Folder 17)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Messages of Congratulations, Sypmathy, Etc., 1963 (Box 67, Folder 18)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Messages of Congratulations, Sypmathy, Etc., 1964 (Box 67, Folder 19)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Miscellaneious Correspondence, 1959-1961 (Box 67, Folder 20)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Papers Left with Msgr. Corcoran, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 21)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Personal Correspondence, 1961-1962 (Box 67, Folder 22)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Personal, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 23)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Personal, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 24)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Personal, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 25)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Photographs, Biographical Material, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 26)
      Though labelled as containing photos none present.
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Secretary's Report, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 27)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Testimony before Congressional Committees (1), 1962 (Box 67, Folder 28)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Testimony before Congressional Committees (2), 1962 (Box 67, Folder 29)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Testimony before Congressional Committees, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 30)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Testimony before Congressional Committees, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 31)
    - Gallagher, Msgr. Raymond J.: Testimony before Congressional Committees, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 32)
    - Goals for Services to Children in Catholic Institutions, 1963 (Box 67, Folder 33)
    - Golden Years Foundation, 1964-1965 (Box 67, Folder 34)
    - Government Housing and Health Programs for Senior Citizens, 1963-1965 (Box 67, Folder 35)
    - Guides for Catholic Day Care Centers, 1964-1965 (Box 67, Folder 36)
    - Guides for Catholic Homes for the Aging, 1963-1965 (Box 67, Folder 37)
    - Guides for Services to Children in Catholic Institutions, 1964 (Box 67, Folder 38)
    - Guilfoyle, Msgr. George H., 1961 (Box 67, Folder 39)
    - HA-HE, 1961-1963 (Box 67, Folder 40)
    - HA-HE, 1964-1965 (Box 67, Folder 41)
    - HA-HE, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 42)
    - HA-HE, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 43)
    - HA-HE, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 44)
    - HA-HE, 1969-1970 (Box 67, Folder 45)
    - HA-HE, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 46)
    - HI-HO-HU-HY, 1961-1964 (Box 67, Folder 47)
    - HI-HO-HU-HY, 1965 (Box 67, Folder 48)
    - HI-HO-HU-HY, 1966 (Box 67, Folder 49)
    - HI-HO-HU-HY, 1967 (Box 67, Folder 50)
    - HI-HO-HU-HY, 1968 (Box 67, Folder 51)
    - HI-HO-HU-HY, 1969-1970 (Box 67, Folder 52)
    - HI-HO-HU-HY, 1975 (Box 67, Folder 53)
    - Harrington, Rev. Timothy J., 1973 (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - Harvey, Canon, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - Hinkel, John V., 1967 (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Hogg Foundation, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 4)
    - Holy Father's Visit, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 5)
    - Hotels, 1967-1968 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Housing, 1964 (Box 68, Folder 7)
    - Housing and Urban Development (HUD): General, 1966-1968 (Box 68, Folder 8)
    - Housing and Urban Development (HUD): Organizational Structure for Implementing the President's Plan for Voluntary Action, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 9)
    - Howes, Rev. Robert G., 1962-1963 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Human Rights Year, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Hunger, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - 'Hunger and Economic Justice,'-Georgetown University, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - I-J, 1961-1963 (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - I-J, 1964-1965 (Box 68, Folder 15)
    - I-J, 1966 (Box 68, Folder 16)
    - I-J, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 17)
    - I-J, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 18)
    - I-J, 1969-1970 (Box 68, Folder 19)
    - I-J, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 20)
    - Independent Sector, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 21)
    - Insignia, 1963-1967 (Box 68, Folder 22)
    - Institute of Salesian Studies, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 23)
    - Institute on Aging-NCCC-Catholic Hospital Association, 1966-1967 (Box 68, Folder 24)
    - Institute on Federal Programs-NCCC-Lutheran Churches, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 25)
    - Institutions-NCCC Task Forces Meeting, New York, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 26)
    - Inter-Diocesan Meeting, Brooklyn, 1965-1967 (Box 68, Folder 27)
    - Interim Interreligious Planning Committee Against Poverty, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 28)
    - International Conference of Social Work, 1962-1965 (Box 68, Folder 29)
    - International Conference of Social Work, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 30)
    - International Conference of Social Work (1), 1966 (Box 68, Folder 31)
    - International Conference of Social Work (2), 1966 (Box 68, Folder 32)
    - International Conference of Social Work (3), 1966 (Box 68, Folder 33)
    - International Conference of Social Work (4), 1966 (Box 68, Folder 34)
    - International Conference of Social Work: U.S. Committee, 1967-1969 (Box 68, Folder 35)
    - International Conference on the Family, 1967 (Box 68, Folder 36)
    - International Council on Social Welfare, 1967-1970 (Box 68, Folder 37)
    - International Federation of Catholic Alumnae (IFCA), 1963 (Box 68, Folder 38)
    - International Society for Community Development, 1968 (Box 68, Folder 39)
    - International Year of the Child, 1976-1979 (Box 68, Folder 40)
    - Interoffice Memos, 1964-1965 (Box 68, Folder 41)
    - Inter-Religious Coalition for Housing, 1975 (Box 68, Folder 42)
    - Invitations, 1977 (Box 68, Folder 43)
    - Iowa Catholic Conference, 1970 (Box 68, Folder 44)
    - Jarmack, Rev. Philip A., 1967 (Box 68, Folder 45)
    - Jarmack, Rev. Philip A., 1968 (Box 68, Folder 46)
    - Jarmack, Rev. Phillip A., 1969-1972 (Box 68, Folder 47)
    - Johnson, Msgr. William R.-NCCC Presdient, 1965 (Box 68, Folder 48)
    - Joint Commission on Correctional Manpower and Training, 1965-1966 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - Joint Commission on Mental Health of Children, 1965-1967 (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Joint Commission on Mental Health of Children (1), 1968-1969 (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Joint Commission on Mental Health of Children (2), 1968-1969 (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - K, 1961-1963 (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - K, 1964-1965 (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - K, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - K, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - K, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - K, 1969-1970 (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - K, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - Kelley, Richard M.-NCCC President, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - Kelley, Richard M., 1974 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - Kerby Guild, The, 1963 (Box 69, Folder 14)
    - Kolka, Msgr. Elmer-NCCC President, 1962-1963 (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Korry, Edward M., Ambassador to Ethiopia, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - L, 1961-1963 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - L, 1964 (Box 69, Folder 18)
    - L, 1965 (Box 69, Folder 19)
    - L, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 20)
    - L, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 21)
    - L, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 22)
    - L, 1969-1971 (Box 69, Folder 23)
    - L, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 24)
    - Labor Department, U.S.: Manpower Administration, 1974-1975 (Box 69, Folder 25)
    - Lambert, Rev. Rollins, 1969-1970 (Box 69, Folder 26)
    - Latin American Congress of Charity, Guatamala, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 27)
    - Library (NCCC), 1963-1964 (Box 69, Folder 28)
    - Lists, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 29)
    - Lobo Case: Rev. Gilbert Rego, New Delhi, India, 1968-1969 (Box 69, Folder 30)
    - Lohmann, Msgr. H. P., 1962 (Box 69, Folder 31)
    - Lutheran Church in America: Board of Social Ministry, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 32)
    - Lutheran Church in America: Board of Social Ministry, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 33)
    - Lutheran Social Welfare Conference, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 34)
    - MA-MC, 1961-1963 (Box 69, Folder 35)
    - MA-MC, 1964-1965 (Box 69, Folder 36)
    - MA-MC, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 37)
    - MA-MC, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 38)
    - MA-MC, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 39)
    - MA-MC, 1969-1970 (Box 69, Folder 40)
    - MA-MC, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 41)
    - Mailgram, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 42)
    - Massachusetts-Cuts in Welfare Funding, 1969 (Box 69, Folder 43)
    - ME-MI-MO-MY, 1961-1963 (Box 69, Folder 44)
    - ME-MI-MO-MY, 1964-1965 (Box 69, Folder 45)
    - ME-MI-MO-MY, 1966 (Box 69, Folder 46)
    - ME-MI-MO-MY, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 47)
    - ME-MI-MO-MY, 1968 (Box 69, Folder 48)
    - ME-MI-MO-MY, 1969-1970 (Box 69, Folder 49)
    - ME-MI-MO-MY, 1975 (Box 69, Folder 50)
    - Merkle Press, 1967 (Box 69, Folder 51)